Inventory of the Gordon Leo McDonough papers 0366
USC Libraries Special Collections
- File of ROLL RECORD
  - DEFENSE AUTHORIZATIONS S 2311 H Res 395
    additional appropriations for aircraft, missiles naval vessels
  - DELAWARE RIVER BASIN COMPACT H J Res 225 H Res 363
  - D C LEGISLATION H R 5486 7154 7218 7053
    D C Clegymen, D C dogs, D C police strenght, evidence admissibility
  - EVACUATED FEDERAL EMPLOYEESH R 2555
    pay in emergency evacuations
  - FARM PROGRAM S 1643 agricultutal act, '61
  - FEDERAL COMMUNICATIONS COMMISSION HR 7856 S 2034 H Res 400
    amend communications act 1934
  - FEED GRAINS PROGRAM H R 4510
    authorize up to 50% of payments in advance of performance by participants, bar planting of popcorn on withdrawn acres
  - FOURTH SUPPLEMENTAL APPROPRIATIONS H R 7712 Defense, state, justice, tresury department
  - HOUSING S S Con Res 30 moderate low income famalies a.o., 1922
  - HOUSING H R 6028 see list on enveloppe
  - INTERNATIONAL TRAVEL H R 4614 office of international travel tourism in dept. of commerce
  - I C C ORDER REVIEW H R 8033H H Res 401
    amend section 17 interstate commerce act
  - MEMBERS FLAG H Res 354
  - MEXICAN FARM LABOR H R 2010 extension of program
  - MILITARY CONSTRUCTION APPROPRIATIONS H R 8302
    research laboratory Wright- Patterson air force base, transfer food container institute of Chicago to Nattick
  - MINIMUM WAGES H R 3935 increase to $ 1.25 an hour
  - MISSIPPIE RIVER BRIDGES H R5963 H Res 352
    general bridge act 1946, Sacramento river bridges.
  - NORTHEASTERN COMPACT H R 30 H Res 378
    water related land resouces
  - PEACE CORPS H R 7500 provide for a Peace Corps
  - READY RESERVE S J Res 120 active duty, members
  - REORGANIZATION PLAN nr 4 (F T C) H Res 305 Federal Trade Commission
  - REORGANIZATION PLAN nr 3 (CAB) H Res 304 Civil Aeronautics Board
  - REORGANIZATION PLAN nr 2 (FCC) H Res 303 Federal Communications Commission
  - REORGANIZATION PLAN nr 1 (SEC) H Res 302 Security Exchange Commission
  - REORGANIZATION (MARITIME FUNCTION) H Res 336 committe on government operations
  - RULES COMMITTEE VOTE congressional record
  - SOCIAL SECURITY AMENDMENTS H R 6027 6283 H Res 258
    additional persons eligible for benefits, disability programs, old age, improve benefits
  - STATE, JUSTICE, JUDICIARY APPROPRIATIONS H R 7371
  - SUSPENSION PASSAGES H R 6765 3385 S 1619
    international finace corp., old currency adjustement, research apparatus imports
  - SUSPENSION PASSAGES H R 6111 H Con Res 209 226
    Cuba, Cuban refugee's students relief, duty free allowance reduction
  - SUSPENSION PASSAGES H R 187 deportation order review
  - TAX RATE EXTENSION H R 7446 H Res 330
    I year extension of excisting corporate normal tan rate excise taxes, transportation tax on persons
  - UNEMPLOYMENT COMPENSATION EXTENSION H R 4806 H Res 195
    temporary raise in rate of federal un-employment tax un-employment compensation
  - WATER POLLUTION CONTROL H R 6441 H Res 274
    amend federal water pollution act, field laboratory/research facilities middle Antlantic area
  - A E C AUTHORIZATIONS H Res 404 H R 7576
    military emergency sales
  - FREEDMAN's HOSPITAL TRANSFER H R 6302 H Res 405
    teaching hospital for Howard university
  - LABOR DEPT. S 1815 H R 6882 H Res 406
    additional secretary of labor in dept. of laboratories
  - LATIN -AMERCAN AID H R 6518
    appropriations inter- american social economic cooperation program, Chilean re-construction and rehabilitation program
  - DEBT LIMIT INCREASE H R 7677 1 year increase- 13 billion
  - FOREIGN AID AUTHORIZATIONS H R 8400 see listing on enveloppe
  - RAILROAD EXPRESS REVENUE INFORMATION H R 1986 H Res 301
    interstate commerce commission, railroad revenues, express companies
  - A E C AUTHORIZATION H R 11974 H Res 716
    appropriations Atomic Energy Commission, prohibit agreement to authorize private industry construction Hanford Wash. reactor, van Zant amendment
  - A E C AUTHORIZATION H R 11949
    appropriations A E C, atomic energy act 1954, Hanford reactor.
  - AGRICULTURE APPROPRIATIONS HR 12648 for, 1963
  - ALL CHANNEL RECIEVERS T V H R 8031
    amend communications act '34, federal communications commission regulatory authority T V receiving apparatus
  - ANTI TRUST EVIDENCE (2 eveloppes) S 167 H Res 558
    documentary evidence required investigation/enforcement anti trust laws
  - CLEAR CHANNEL OPERATIONS H Res 714 F C C authorization class I -A
  - COMMERCE DEPT HR 6360 H Res 425
    additional secretary of Commerce
  - COMMUNICATIONS SATTELITE SYSTEM H R 1104 (see enveloppe)
  - DEBT LIMIT INCREASE H R 11990 12026
    temporary increase of publicdebt limit
  - DEBT LIMIT INCREASE H R 10050 H Res 549
    temporary increase of public debt limit
  - DEFENSE PRODUCTION H R 11500 H Res 708 S 3203
    amend extend defense production act '50 for 2 years
  - D C JUVENILLE COURT H R 6747 S 486
    amendjuvenile court court act D C, additional judge D C juvenile court
  - D C TAXES H R 258 increase D C sales tax from 3 to 3%, transfer certain parking fees a. o. tochighway fund.
  - EDUCATIONAL TELEVISION H R 132 H Res 552 S 205
    fedral matching grants construction T V facilities used for educational purposes.
  - EXPORTS CONTROL H R 11309 S 1361 H Res 707
    3 years continuation authority regulation exports
  - FARM BILL H R 12391 H Res 727 food agricultur act (see specification on enveloppe, '62
  - FEDERAL RESERVE S 1005 H Res 5749
    construction federal reserve bankbranch approval FRB, limit on construction of braches of FRB from 30 to 60 million.
  - FEDRAL-AID HIGHWAYS H R 12135 H Res 723
    appropriations 1964/65, Baldwin amendment, families displaced by right-of- way acquisitions
  - FOREIGN AID AUTHORIZATION S 2996
  - FOREIGN AID AUTHORIZATION S 2996 (see enveloppe)
  - FOREIGN AID AUTHORIZATION H R 9033 appropriations foreign assistanee
  - GAMBLING DEVICES S 1658 H Res 698 prohibition of transportation in interstate foreign commerce
  - GRAND CANYON NATIONAL PARK S 383
    acquisition of patented mining claims
  - HIGHER EDUCATION AID H R 8900 H Res 527 625, (2 enveloppes)
    assistance to public nonprofit insttutions of higher education with construction, rehabilition improvement of facilities.
  - IDAHO RECLAMATION H R 529 S 405 H Res729
    Mann creek fedral reclamation project
  - INDEPENDANT OFFICES APPROPRIATIONS H R 12711
  - INTERNATIONAL MONETARY FUND H R 10162
    amend Bretton- Woods agreement act, U S particification in loans to fund.
  - LABUR-HEW APPROPRIATIONS H R 10904 adoption of conference report
  - LEGISLATIVE APPROPRIATIONS H R 11151 alotment of funds fiscal year, '63
  - MANPOWER RESOURCES H R8399 S (see enveloppe), 1991
  - MILITARY PROCUREMENT H R 9751 H Res 563 appropriations fiscal year [UNK] for aircraft, missiles naval vessels.
  - MILITARY PROCUREMENT H R 5532 H Res 667 amend armed services procurement act, '47
  - NASA AUTHORIZATION H R 11737 H Res 648 appropriations for NASA, '63
  - NASA AUTHORIZATION H R 6874H Con Res 355 appropriations for NASA, '63
  - NEW YORK CITY EXPENSES HR 4441 H Res 575
    appropriations as ex-gratia payments for extra-ordinary expenses '51 general assembly of U N
  - OREGON RECLAMATION H R 575
    Baker federal reclamation project, Oregon
  - HOUSING FOR THE ELDERLY H R 12628
    Housing act 1959, provide low moderate cost housing.
  - LABOR -HEW APPROPRIATIONS H R 10904
    Barring of funds under regylations of lobbying act, rejection amendment to bar hospital contruction funds to states practising segregation.
  - PACIFIC ISLANDS TRUST TERRITORY S 2775
    Remove ceiling on authorizations for Territory
  - PEACE CORPS H R 10700 H Res 579
    Amend Peace Coros Act, appropriations for carrying out programs.
  - PHILIPPINE WAR DAMAGES AWARDS H R 8617 H Res 627 (see listing on enveloppe)
  - POLL TAX S J Res 29 Outlawing poll tax as qualification for voting in Federal elections.
  - PUBLIC WORKS ACCELERATION H R 10113 S 2965
    Prevent construction of schools under act, 75% of construction contribution when state/local body unable provide 50%
  - REORGANIZATION (NLRB) H Res 328
    Disapprove reorganization plan 5 1961, National Labor Relations Board.
  - REORGANIZATION PLAN nr 1 (URBAN AFFAIRS) H Res 530
    Disapprove plan I, new Deot of Urban Affairs Housing.
  - SCHOOL LUNCH PROGRAM H R 1165
    Apportion cash assistance funds among states under school lunch act.
  - SCIENCE MEDAL RECIPIETS H R 4055
    Authorization of monetary awards
  - SECOND SUPPLEMENTAL APPROPRIATIONS H R 11038 (see list on envelioppe)
  - SOCIAL SECURITY H R 10616 H Res 363
    Extend improve public assistance, child welfare program of social security act.
  - STATE, JUSTICE, COOMERCE JUDICIARY APPROPRIATIONS H R 12589
    Construction Rama Road in Nicaragua, reduce fund for educational exchange activities, maximum payment entertainers in cultural exchange, Supreme funds for bible purchase.
  - SUGAR H R 8050 H Res 726
    Importation of honey bees, sugar quotas for certain Western Hemisphere countries
  - SUGAR H R 12154 Amend provisions of sugar act fees on non quotas sugar purchasement by U S. [UNK], 1945
  - SUPPLEMENTAL AIRCARRIERS, 1969
    Amend Federal Aviation ACt 1958
  - TAX REVISION H Res 576 H R 10650
    Closed rule waving points of order, amend internal revenue code 1954, credit for investement in depreciable property, eliminate defects inequalities.
  - TRADE EXPANSION H R 11970
    trade expansion act 1962. 1961
  - TEXTILE IMPORTS REGULATION H R 10788
    Amend section 204 of agricultural act 1956, regulation of textile imports.
  - VESSALS CONSTRUCTION SUBSIDIES H R 11386
    Amend section 502 Merchant Marine Act 1936
  - WAR CLAIMS H R 7283 H Res 746
    Amenment war claims act 1948, administrative expenses pai from alien propert fund, compensation for certain World War 2 losses.
  - WELFARE PENSION PLANS DISCLOSURE HR 8723
    Amend welfare pension plans, diclosure act with respect to enforcement o.a.
  - AIRPORTS - FEDRAL ASSISTANCE HR 8102 Civil functions under Dept of Army Dept of Interior, upper Colorado River Basin, A E C, T V A.
  - AIRPORTS -FEDRAL ASSISTANCE HR 8102 amend federal airport act, extension of time for grants
  - ARMS CONTROL H R 9118 7377 S 2180 H RES 462 (see lising on envelopped)
  - ARMS CONTROL AGENCY H R 9118 establish U S arms control agency
  - A E C AUTHORIZATIONS H R 7576 appropriations A E C
  - CIVIL SERVICE - SUPERGRADES H R 7377 H Con Res 399 (seelisting on envelope)
  - CIVIL SERVICE - SUPERGRADES H R 7377
    Compensation of hearing examiners, number of positions in top grade of classification act o4 1949, special rates of pay scientists engeneers.
  - COMMUNIST CHINA S Con Res 34
    seating of China in U N
  - DEFENSE APPROPRIATIONS H R 7581
    civil defense funds for 1962
  - D C TAXES HR 258 increase sales tax from 2 to 3%, transfer of parkingfees to highway fund
  - EDUCATIONAL AID HR 8890 emergency education act, 1961
  - EDUCATION-FEDERALLY IMPACTED AREAS S2393
    N [UNK] E A, assistance for schools, national defense education act
  - EDUCATIONAL CULTURAL EXCHANGE H R 8666
    international relations of USA
  - FEED GRAN PROGRAM H R 8914
    amend soil conservation domestic allotent [UNK]
  - FEDERAADVISORY COUNCIL ON THE ARTS HR 4172
    developmentof fine arts in capital U S
  - FISHING CENTER ACQYARIUM H R 8181
    national center in D C
  - FOREIGN AGENTS REGRISTATION H R 5751
    amend subversive activities control act 1950
  - FOREIGN AID APPROPRIATIONS H R 9033 (see listing on enveloppe)
  - FOREIGN AID AUTHORIZATIONS S 1983 adoption conference report
  - HAWAIIAN BOTANIC GARDEN H R 5628 establishing National tropical botanic gardens
  - HOG CHOLERA ERADICATION HR 7176 S 1908 H RES 435
    national program for...
  - JUSTICE DEPT ATTORNEYS H R 6242 lump-sum readjustment payments Reserve persons
  - JUVENILE DELINQUENCY H r 8028 H RES 436
    juvenile delinquency outh offenses,control act,projects D C grants restrictions
  - LEAD ZINC MINING H R 84 H RES 424
    stabilize MINING by small domestic producers
  - MEXICAN FARM LABOR PROGRAM H RES455 H R 2010
    amendagriculture act 1949, extand program
  - MILITARY CONSTRUCTION APPROPRIATIONS H R 8302
    development center Natick Mass. [UNK]
  - NEW YORK WORLD FAIR H R 7763 participation of U S
  - RESERVE PERSONNEL H R 8773 H Res 437
    lump-sum readjustement payments Reserce personnel
  - PEACE CORPS H R 7500 see listingon enveloppe
  - POSTAGE REVISION H Res 464 H R 7927
    adjust postal rates,open closed waiving points of order
  - POSTAL PAY S 1459 longevity step increases
  - SUSPENSION PASSAGES HR 9000
    extension public laws 81-815 81-874, impact area relief, national defense education act
  - WELFARE PENSION PLANS DISCLOSURE H R 8723
    amend WPPD act, additional sanctions, method of enforement
  - STATE, JUSTICE, JUDICIARY APPROPRIATIONS H R 7371
    civil rights commission
  - PUBLIC WORKS APPROPRIATIONS H R 9076
    A E C, civil functions under Dept of army, Dept of Interior, T V A, upper Colorado River basin.
- General file by SUBJECTS in boxes 63-68
  In folders with headers
  Arranged alphabetically by folder
  - General file by SUBJECT, 1945-62
    A - Co in folders with headers
    Arranged aphabetically by folders Horizontal arr.: Subject, year(s) of correspondance related bills, related subject
    - CALIFORNIA STATE AFFAIRS H R 132 1565 5173 AJR 9 29 35 37 38 39 SJR 30 32 33 36 41 SA 1748 SR 153, 1953 (Box Box 63)
      Civil defense, collection of tolls S F Oakland bay briges, federal authotities encroachment on states rights, major California taxes, sleeping sicness, trans Sierra highway program, use of fedral lands by public agencies in California, world trade policy
    - CALIFORNIA STATE AFFAIRS H R 1254 5915 5955 5999 6106 7764, 1954
      Cost of government state of California by dept., federal Stamp tax, long term leases public lands to states, snow water supply forecast, report committee constituonal aspects of international agreements U N states coast geodetic survey, views of California on Colorado riverstorage project
    - CALIFORNIA STATE AFFAIRS H R 162 598 1819 3257 3322 11170 S 756, 1955
      California public survey, control insect, pests plant diseases, divert water from Trinity river to Central Vally-irrigation, Feather river project, fedral regulation of natural gas producers, labor statitstics bulletin, military status officers public health service, Mill vally highway- proposedroute into L A San Gabriel mountains, Barstov, Mojave, trinity river project, vocational rehabilitation, water conversation development,
      Forest fire protection, review of civil defensess, state of Calif. general fund cash condition.
    - CALIFORNIA STATE AFFAIRS H R 7573 7574 S 863, 1956
      Beach ersosion, Central Vally project, Douglas Aircraft Company, Feather River projects, Federal States government water rights, S 863 analyses, Fedral State Social Securuty formula, flood control dams, funds apportionments, highway user tax, Potrero Hill project, San Louis project, Woodlake Terminus Suc cess dams, Tulare county San Yoaquin vally
    - CALIFORNIA STATE AFFAIRS HR 6659 7576 9512 9530, 1958 '57
      Civil defense, federal supervision of Californian Indians, San louis- central vally project, Santa Margarita watershed, small craft harbors commission meeting, Social Security Act- OASI coverage, soil water conservation laboratory in Calif., Stanislaus -Santa Clara roads, state of California economic surveys, State Colleges residence program, trans Sierra Highway project, Trinity River project.
      Monterey harbor.
    - CALIFORNIA STATE AFFAIRS S 44, 1959 '58 '60 '62
      California highway control program, California marketing act, California water resources development, program, dept, of water resources [UNK] phlet, Feather River water rpoject, Federal re clamations laws, FEPC legislation, Federal [UNK] Fund, National Forests, Sacramento River [UNK] control project, saline water conversion demonstration plans.
    - CALIFORNIA STATE AFFAIRS, 1961-62
      Connolly amendment, dam at Pittsburg, emergen cy stockpiles of food, grains, drugs etc., public policy regarding agricultural chemicals, repair Navy 75% in private shipyards.
    - California Tax payers Ass., 1957
      Trinity project
      Powerfacilities private enterprise.
    - Cathlic Affairs, 1958 '49 '50 '53
      Catholic Parochial taxations, persecution non-cathlics in Columbia, subversive action of Vati can, Waters-Hollibaugh bill.
    - CENSUS DATA, 1950
    - CENSUS DATA, 1955
    - CHINA AFFAIRS, 1956
      Commission of millions against admission of Red CHina to U N, trade with Red China, expanding trade attacked.
    - CIVIL AIR PATROL
    - CIVIL AIR PATROL Public Law 557, California waing CAP, 1955 '57
    - Civil defense matters Facts about fall-out, U S civil defence council, 1955
    - Congressional calendar list, 1961
    - Congressional calendar Directory list, 1949
    - Congressional calendar Directory list, 1951
    - Congressional Directory, 1953
    - Congressional Directory, 1961
    - Congressional Directory list 86 Congress, 1961
    - Congressional Library, 1946 '47
    - Congressional Record List 82 Congress 51, 1950%
    - Congressional Record List, 1953 '54
    - COAST GUARD AFFAIRS Coat Guard academy, informative booklets, photo's, 1947
    - AGRICULTURAL YEARBOOK Farmers Bulletin, Science in farming publication, 1947
    - AGRICULTURE DEPT National rural electric cooperative ass., 1948 '49
    - AGRICULTURE DEPT Forest service photographs, 1948 '49
    - AGRICULTURE DEPT Publications procedures in ordering publications, 1950 '45
    - AIRCRAFT INDUSTRY, 1948 '50 '52 '53
      Airline pilots association recommendations for safety, airports projects, Boeing booklet, Boeing sub-sonic transport jets, Federal airport project independant Air Safety Board in Congress HR 556 dispersal of aircraft plants from Pacific Coast
    - AIRFORCE Photograph story data Security violation, 8 miles over LA, 1950
    - American Legion Affairs, 1956
    - California delegation Mexican-Amercan ailine receprocity, 1957
      American flag carrier servie L A Mexico City, Aviation Week views, complaints to Civil Aeronaitic Board, status of airline operations Western airline to Mexico City.
    - California Merchant Marine Calif. Maritime Academy, Calif. maritime indus, 1949
    - BALTIC STATES AFFAIRS, 1961 '62
      deportations of Lithuanians, Latvians, Estonians
    - BEYLORUSSIAN AFFAIRS, 1960 '61 '62
      Anniversary of independance, ommision of [UNK] language in broadcast Voice of America
    - Bridges, Harry deportation-citizens case, pamphlet, 1945
    - Budget Cartoons newspapers clippings, 1945
    - CAPTIVE NATION (general) Captive Nations Week President's proclimation., 1961
    - Congressional calendar list 2, 1961
  - General file by SUBJECT Co - Sp in folders with headings, 1945-62
    Arranged alphabetically by folders Horizontal arr.: subject, year(s) of correspondance, related bill(s), related subject
    - CONGRESSIONAL RECORD LIST 84th Congress, 1954 '55 '56 (Box Box 64)
    - CONGRESSIONAL RECORD LIST 85th Congress HR 1195 2017, 1957 '58
    - CONGRESSIONAL RECORD LIST 86th Congress, 1958 '59 '60
    - CONGRESSIONAL RECORD LIST, 1961
    - CUBAN AFFAIRS Government of Venezuela, letters to US congress from former members of Cuban Congress, U S Batista support, 1961
    - CYPRESS AFFAIRS British rule of Cypress, commentary on Cypress questi Justive for Cypress Committee, legal, position of Cypress., 1954 '55
    - CZECHOSLOVAKIA AFFAIRS, 1955 '56 '
      Council of free CZECHOSLOVIA, House of Congress state ments, Masaryk founder of the Republic.
    - DATA used to prepare records statements Hongkong trade distribution Philippines South Asia, illicit narcotic treffic in Far East-opium, heroin, lists of seizure of narcotics, organizations-heroin to Singapore, smuggle heroin into Japan - US, U. N. Commission on narcotic drugs., 1953
    - DAUGHTERS OF AMERICAN REVOLUTION, 1949 '55 '56
      Constitution week, resolutions adepted 1956
    - EARTHQUAKE SAFETY MEASURES, 1955
      Recommended program in engeneering Seismology.
    - FEDERAL DEPOSIT INSURANCE CORPORATIONS, 1951
      Banks in suspension 1917- 1933, banks placed on receivers lists 1934- 50, comparison of capital ratios 1945 1950
    - FEDERAL HOUSING ADMINISTRATION, 1949
      Mutual Housing Association
    - FEDERAL TRADE COMMISSION, 1949
      Elmo Sales Corporation
    - GERITY FILE D J 7-6697, 1961
      Public Facilities Financing
    - GROMAN, Harry, 1950
      Loan for mausoleum at Hillside Memorial Park
    - GUAM AFFAIRS 1st legislature of Guam, 1953
    - HAWAIAN AFFAIRS H R 5093 S 2216, 1949 '50
      Communist penetration of Hawai islands, Harry Bridges ILWU longshormen's strike, re appointment of Governer Stainback
    - INDIAN AFFAIRS 52 H R 6908 7232 S 2780, 1950 '
      Blackfeet tribe, Governers interstate Indian Council statements, relgious freedom, health facilities education, Indian Bureau, tranfer Indian Health Service from Dept. of Interior to U S Public Health Service, tribal affairs, treaty violations.
    - HUNGARIAN AFFAIRS H R 99 4581 5849, 1956 '57 '60 '61
      Captive nations week, Committee for Hugarian leberation memoran-memorandum, Emergency committee for U N action on Hungary, fifth anniversary of Hungarian Revolution, Hungarian veterans in U S, Cardinal Mindszenty arrest diplomatic protests, report U N campaign on expelling Hungaran delegation from U N.
    - IRISH AFFAIRS HR 19, 1951 '53 '54 '55 '56 '57 '59
      Fogarty discharge petitions: pamplets Irelands right to unity, the unity of Ireland, Ireland North Atlantic Defense, Irish information bulletins: unification North South: North against, removal tariff quotas on imported woollen worsted fabrics
    - ITALIAN AFFAIRS H R 2081 Chistopher Columbus, 1949
    - ITALIAN AMERICAN AFFAIRS H R 2081, 1951
      Christopher Columbus memorial in Washington D C, citizens committee for memorial memorandum.
    - JAPANESE AFFAIRS, 1950 '51 '56
      Japanese evacuation claims program, Nisei G I 's, Tokyo Rose
    - JEWISH AFFAIRS H R 3258 3488 7308 S 1247, 1950 '51 '52 '57 '59 '60
      Aid to Israel, anti defamation leage of B' nai B'rith, arms sales to Israel Egypt, Chatman amenment-reduce funds for Israel, Israel Egypt relations survey, memorandum on aid to Near East, Middle East situ ation, mutual security plan, pamplet- violence Jordan Israel border, Zionisme.
    - JUDICIAL DECISIONS, 1957
      F B I files opening, Suprmeme court decisions Communist party.
    - LEGISLATIVE RECORD of Mc Donough 85th Congress, 1957-58
    - LOBBYISTS REGRISTRATION direct Airline Service L A Europe K L M, 1953
    - LITHAUNIAN AFFAIRS, 1954 '55 '57 '58 '59 '60 '62
      Congressional Record 85 Congress 1958, pamplets; freedom for Lithuanians, communist take over occupation of Lithaunia, Lithuanian's independance day.
    - LOS ANGELES AIRPORT Global Air Harbor Committee
    - LOS ANGELES CHAMBER OF COMMERCE, 1958
      International exposition in South California, roster Engeneering Consultants Committee.
    - LOS ANGELES CIVIL DEFENSE, 1953
      Civil defense disaster corps city of L A 1952, news-letter
    - LOS ANGELES CITY AFFAIRS, 1956 '55 '57 '58
      Banning homes project site, Brighton - Brilt homes, California Air National Guard, City Dodger contract, Feather River project, Naval Supply Dept. San Pedro.
    - LOS ANGELES CITY AFFAIRS H R 2892 2720 3238 7782 SB 859 P B 21 Public Law 352 889, 1956 '54